Printed Maps Printed.Maps
American Philosophical Society
- North America
  - United States Of America
    - A map of the United States: compiled chiefly from the state maps, and other authentic information, by Sam'l Lewis. 1795. Philadelphia: M. Carey: 1795., 554; Size: 61.7 x 89 cm.; Samuel Lewis.; W. Harrison.
      Inset: Florida and the Gulf coast past New Orleans.
      See: Mathew Carey, General atlas. Philadelphia: M. Carey: 1796, no. 24.
    - A map of the United States, exhibiting the post-roads, the situations, connections & distances of the post-offices stage roads, counties, ports of entry and delivery for foreign vessels, and the principal rivers. By Abraham Bradley, Junr., [1796].; 555; Scale: 1 cm. = 15 mi.; Size of paper: 89 x 94.4 cm.; Abraham Bradley, Jr.; William Harrison, Jr.
      Inset: Progress of the mail on the main line.
      Wheat: 128
    - The United States of America. [1796]., 556; Scale: 2.5 cm. = 150 mi.; Size: 24.9 x 32.5 cm.; W. Barker.
      See: Mathew Carey, Carey's American pocket atlas, following p. 4.
      Wheat: 131
      Presented by Suzanne Wister Eastwick and Joseph L. Eastwick, July 1975.
    - Map of the United States, Canada &c. intended to illustrate the travels of the Duke de la Rochefoucauld Liancourt. London: R. Phillips: 1799 [1 July 1799]., 557; Scale: 69½ English mi. = 1 degree.; Size: 40.5 x 42.3 cm.; Smith and Jones and T. Foot.
      Photostat.
      On map in ink: "Rapport sur les Archives de France, relative à l'histoire du Canada, par J. Edmond Roy - Canada - Public Archives, pub. no. 6-1911."
      See: La Rochefoucauld Liancourt, F. A. F., duc de, Travels through the United States. London: R. Phillips: 1799.
    - The United States of America. [1799]., 558; Scale: 2.5 cm. = 150 mi.; Size: 24.7 x 31.1 cm.
      In: John Payne, A new and complete system of universal geography, vol. 4, opposite p. 50.
      Wheat: 142
    - Map of the United States, exhibiting the post-roads, the situations, connexions and distances of the post-offices stage roads, counties & principal rivers. By Abraham Bradley, Junr. District of Columbia: 1804., 559; Scale: 1 in. = 30 mi.; Size: 95 x 132.2 cm.; Colored.; Abraham Bradley, Jr.
      Inset: Map of North America.
      This map was first published in 1796. See map No. 555 above.
    - A map of part of the continent of North America from longitude [blank] w. of Washington City to the Pacific and between lattitude 35 and 52 north compiled from the information of the best informed travellers through that quarter of the Globe in which, the Missouri Jefferson Lewis and the upper part of the Clarks river and the lower part of the Columbia River is [partially?] corrected by celestial observations from the junction of the Missouri and Mississippi to the enterance of the Columbia into the pacific ocean in Longitude 47° 57' west of Washington City and 124° 57" west of Greenwich and in Lattitude 46° 19' 11" north. Showing Lewis and Clarks rout over the Rocky Mountains in 1805 on their rout to the pacific from the United States. By William Clark. [Meriden Gravure: ca. 1950]., 560; 4 sheets.; Scale: 1 in. = 50 mi.; Size: 147.6 x 262.7 cm.; Colored.; William Clark.
      Facsimile of the original manuscript map in the William Robertson Coe collection of Western Americana, Yale University Library, 1950.
    - New map of the United States of America including part of Louisiana drawn from the latest authorities. Revised and corrected by Osgood Carleton, Esqr. Boston: John Sullivan: 1806., 561; Size: 121 x 137.6 cm.; Colored.; Osgood Carleton.
      Contains tables of the ports of entry in the United States, and situation and extent of each state.
    - Die Vereinigten Staaten von Nord-America, nach den sichersten Bestimmungen, neuesten Nachrichten und Charten, in der Alber'schen Projection entworfen, von C. G. Reichard. Nürnberg: Homanns: 1809., 562; Scale: 69 English mi. = 1 degree.; Size: 58.9 x 73.8 cm.; Colored.; C. G. Reichard.; C. Trummer.
    - [Map of the United States]. Philadelphia: T. L. Plowman: 1811 [copy 2]., 563; Size: 50.1 x 64.9 cm.
      Two nearly identical copies. Copy 2 marked "2nd Edition. Containing the Seat of War &c."
    - The United States of America confirmed by treaty 1783. London: R. Wilkinson: 1812 [10 February, 1812]., 564; Scale: 1 in. = 150 British statute mi.; Size: 22.2 x 28.3 cm.; Colored.; B. Smith.
      Shows the state of Franklinia.
    - Map of the United States of America. Philadelphia: Melish: 1813 [June 1813]., 565; Scale: 1 in. = 100 mi.; Size: 36.8 x 46.2 cm.; H. S. Tanner.; John Melish.
      In: [Melish], Documents relative to the negotiations for peace between the United States and Great Britain. Philadelphia: Palmer: 1814.
    - A map of Lewis and Clark's track, across the western portion of North America from the Mississippi to the Pacific Ocean. [Philadelphia: 1814]., 566; Size: 30.3 x 70.3 cm.; Samuel Lewis and William Clark.
      Impression from original copper plate in the possession of the American Philosophical Society. It was first printed in 1814 and this pulling from the plate in 1979 is the first supplemental pulling ever done.
      For original pulling, see: History of the expedition under the command of Lewis and Clark... Philadelphia: Bradford and Inskeep; New York: Abrm. H. Inskeep, J. Maxwell: 1814.
    - A map historical and biographical chart. Of the United States by David Ramsay. [Philadelphia: Carey: ca. 1815]., 567; Size: 31.5 x 35.3 cm.; Size of paper: 48.2 x 73.8 cm.; Colored.; David Ramsay.
      Contains map and chart with four columns of text.
      See: Robert L. Brunhouse, "David Ramsey, selections from his writings." American Philosophical Society. Transactions, n.s., vol. 55.
    - A new and correct map of the United States of North America; exhibiting the counties, towns, roads &c. in each state. Carefully compiled from surveys and the most authentic documents, by Samuel Lewis. Philadelphia: Emmor Kimber: 1815., 568; Scale: 69½ American mi. = 1 degree.; Size: 171.5 x 186.5 cm.; Colored.; Samuel Lewis.; W. and S. Harrison.
      Inset: United States boundary, crossing the Lake of the Woods.
      Presented by Emmor Kimber, 3 November 1815.
    - Map of the United States with the contiguous British & Spanish possessions. Compiled from the latest and best authorities by John Melish. Philadelphia: Melish: 1816 [6 June 1816]., 569; Scale: 1 in. = 50 mi.; Size: 89 x 144 cm.; Colored.; John Melish.; Vallance and H. S. Tanner.
      Inset: West Indies.
      Presented by John Melish, 2 December 1816.
    - Map of the United States of America. Designed to illustrate the geological memoir of William Maclure, Esqr. Entered as the Act directs, and published by John Melish, Philadelphia [ca. 1818]., 570; Scale: 1 in. = 90 mi.; Size: 33 x 44.3 cm.; Colored.; William Maclure.
      Published in the Transactions of the American Philosophical Society, vol. 1, n.s., to illustrate William Maclure's geological observations, as read to the Society, 16 May 1817.
      Map shows proposed canals, boundary lines, and roads and distances.
    - United States of America compiled from the latest and best authorities, by John Melish 1819. Philadelphia: Melish: 1819 [10 July 1819]., 571; Scale: 1 in. = 120 mi.; Size: 40.3 x 49 cm.; Colored.; John Melish.; Samuel Harrison.
      Presented by John Melish prior to 1826.
    - Map of the United States with the contiguous British and Spanish possessions compiled from the latest and best authorities by John Melish. Philadelphia: Melish: 1820 [16 June 1820]., 572; Scale: 1 in. = 50 mi.; Size: 107.8 x 142.3 cm.; Colored.; J. Vallance and H. S. Tanner.; John Melish.
    - A map of the United States of America. Philadelphia: H. S. Tanner: [1825]., 573; Scale: 1 in. = 125 mi.; Size: 39 x 65.2 cm.; Colored.; H. S. Tanner.
      Inset: Profile or vertical section of the Erie Canal, exhibiting its various locks, levels...
    - Map of the United States of North America compiled from the latest and most authentic information by David H. Vance. Philadelphia: Anthony Finley: 1825 [12 July 1825]., 574; Size: 131 x 155.3 cm.; Colored.; David H. Vance.; J. H. Young.
      Insets: Map of North America, including all the recent geographical discoveries to 1825; comparative elevations of the principal mountains and hills in the United States.
      Presented by David H. Vance, 21 October 1825.
    - Lay's map of the United States. Compiled from the latest and best authorities and actual surveys by Amos Lay. New York: J. M. Bowen: 1827., 575; Size: 132.5 x 153.5 cm.; Colored.; O. H. and D. S. Throop and William Chapin.; O. H. Throop and Amos Lay.
      Inset: Florida.
      Contains statistical table of the United States.
    - United States of America. Philadelphia: H. S. Tanner: 1829., 576; Size: 117.7 x 151.3 cm.; H. S. Tanner.
      Insets: South part of Florida, and, Oregon and Mandan district. Individual insets of Washington, Baltimore, Philadelphia, New York, Boston, Charleston and New Orleans: environs of Albany, Boston, New York, Philadelphia and Trenton, Baltimore and Washington, and Savannah. Also, profiles of the following canals: Erie, Ohio, Morris (N. J.), Union, Chesapeake and Ohio. Also, profile of Schuylkill navigation, Penna., and the Columbia railroad.
      Presented by Henry Schenck Tanner, 18 September 1829.
    - Mitchell's reference & distance map of the United States by J. H. Young. Published by S. Augustus Mitchell. Philadelphia: Mitchell & Hinman: 1835., 577; Scale: 69.2 mi. = 1 degree.; Size: 32.6 x 170.7 cm.; Colored.; J. H. Young, F. Dankworth, E. Yeager, and E. F. Woodward.; J. H. Young.
      Insets: General map of the United States with the contiguous British and Mexican possessions; vicinity of Boston; vicinity of New York; vicinity of Philadelphia; north part of Maine; south part of Florida; vicinity of Albany; vicinity of Baltimore and Washington; vicinity of Cincinnati; vicinity of Charleston; vicinity of New Orleans; vicinity of the Falls of Niagara; and vicinity of Rochester, N.Y.
      Presented by James H. Young, 15 May 1835. Publisher Mitchell presented a copy, ca. 1837.
    - Skeleton map showing the rail roads completed and in progress in the United States, and those projected through the public lands and their connection with the principal harbours on the lakes and on the seaboard. Printed by order of the Senate of the United States, the 9th Sess., 31st Congress, 1848-49. [Washington]: C. B. Graham, lith.: [1849]., 578; Scale: 4.7 cm. = 100 mi.; Size: 116.9 x 93.4 cm.; Colored.; C. B. Graham.
      This was accompanied with a report from the Hon. Sidney Breeze, for granting the land to the state of Illinois to aid in the completion of her railroads.
    - United States. London, Edinburgh & Dublin: J. & F. Tallis: [ca. 1850]., 579; Scale: 1 in. = 250 mi.; Size: 24.3 x 32.2 cm.; Colored.; J. Rogers and J. Marchant.; John Rapkin.
      Insets: Portraits of Washington and Franklin; the Capitol, Washington; Penn's treaty with the Indians; Buffalo hunt; Washington's monument.
    - Bien & Sterner's new rail road map of the United States and the Canadas compiled from the latest surveys and locations under the direction of Zerah Colburn editor of the Rail Road Advocate. New York: A. Ranney: 1855., 580; Scale: 3½ in. = 200 mi.; Size: 67.9 x 79.5 cm.; Colored.; Bien & Sterner.; Zerah Colburn.
      In: Zerah Colburn, Railroad economy, the revised and extended report on European and American railways. New York: Wynkoop: [1855].
    - Equal magnetic declination for the year 1850. U.S. Coast Survey. A. D. Bache, supdt. N.p.: 1856., 581; Scale: 1:20,000,000.; Size: 16.6 x 25.7 cm.; A. D. Bache.
      Presented by A. D. Bache, 7 March 1857.
    - Lines of equal magnetic dip and horizontal intensity for the year 1850. U.S. Coast Survey. A. D. Bache, supdt. N.p.: 1856., 582; Scale: 1:20,000,000.; Size: 17 x 25.6 cm.; A. D. Bache.
    - J. Sage & Son's new & reliable rail road map comprising all the railroads of the United States and Canadas with their stations and distances, compiled from the most accurate statistics. Buffalo: J. Sage & Sons: 1858., 583; Scale: 1 in. = 33⅓ mi.; Size: 91.2 x 110.8 cm.
      Inset: Eastern Massachusetts, & part of N. Hampshire, Rhode Island & Connecticut. On an enlarged scale.
      Surrounding the maps are the names of various railroads listed by states.
    - Lloyd's new steel plate railroad map of the United States and Canadas from the latest surveys. Showing every railroad & station finished to September 1862. Engraved to accompany Lloyd's R. R. Weekly Guide. New York: J. T. Lloyd: 1862., 584; Scale: 69.1 Statute or American mi. = 1 degree.; Size: 94.5 x 125.3 cm.; Colored.
    - Weather map. U.S. War Department. Signal Service, U.S. Army. Division of Telegrams and Reports for the Benefit of Commerce. Washington: J. L. Kervand, lith.: 1872., 585; Size: 36.5 x 56.8 cm.; Colored.; J. L. Kervand.
      Three copies for Friday, 31 May 1872: 7:35 A.M.; 4:35 P.M.; and 11:35 P.M.
      There are also yellow flimsies filled-in in manuscript.
    - Weather map. U.S. War Department. Signal Service, U.S. Army, Division of Telegrams and Reports for the Benefit of Commerce and Agriculture. All observations made at the same moment of actual (not local) time. 1873-1876. Washington: N. Peters, photo-lithographer: 1873-1876., 586; Scale: 4 cm. = 250 mi.; Size: 36.1 x 56.9 cm.; Colored.; Prof. Guyot.
      Distributed by the Philadelphia Board of Marine Underwriters.
    - Map of the United States and territories, showing the extent of public surveys, Indian and military reservations, land grant R.R., rail roads, canals, and other details... compiled from the official surveys of the U.S. Department of the Interior General Land Office... by C. Roeser. New York: J. Bien: 1879., 587; Scale: 1 in. = 30 mi.; Size: 122.3 x 197 cm.; Colored.; C. Roeser.; J. Bien.
      Inset: Territory of Alaska.
    - New shippers railway map of the United States... showing all railroads, each in a separate color, and all railroad stations in large plain type. Chicago: Rand, McNally & Co.: 1883-1901., 588; 8 sections.; Scale: 1 in. = 8 mi.; Size of each: 300 x 159 cm.
    - Outline map [of the United States] with dials showing standard railway time. Copyrighted 1883 by W. F. Allen. New York: 1883., 589; Size: 15.6 x 22 cm.; Colored.; American Bank Note Company.; W. F. Allen.
    - Colton's railroad & commercial map of the United States & Canada. East of the 100th meridian of longitude. Compiled, engraved and published by G. W. & C. B. Colton & Co. New York: Colton: 1884., 590; Scale: 1 in. = 20 statute mi.; Size: 174.9 x 146.8 cm.; Colored.; G. W. and C. B. Colton.
      Insets: Map of the railroads of New England; vicinity of New York; and general map of the United States, showing the railroad routes across the continent.
      Incomplete: wanting western half.
    - Map showing the rail road and canal lines used in the determination of elevations by James T. Gardner, geographer. [Ca. 1885]., 591; Size: 38 x 56.1 cm.; James T. Gardner.
    - Statistical map of the United States of America. Prepared by James S. Cowden and James D. Holman... under the direction of the Hon. John C. Black, U.S. Pension Bureau, Commissioner of Pensions. July 1888. [Washington: Government Printing Office: 1888]., 592; Size: 48.6 x 77.2 cm.; James S. Cowden, James D. Holman, and John C. Black.
    - Annual change of the magnetic declination for the epoch January, 1890. U.S. Coast and Geodetic Survey. T. C. Mendenhall, superintendent. N.p.: [1889]., 593; Scale: 1:10,000,000.; Size: 36.6 x 51.6 cm.; T. C. Mendenhall and C. A. Schott.
      At head of map: "Coast & Geodetic Survey Report for fiscal year 1887-'88."
    - General railway map of the United States, the Dominion of Canada and Mexico. Every subscriber to the official railway guide for 1889, at $5.00 per annum, will be furnished with a copy of this map on application to the National Railway Publication Co., 41 Bond Street, New York. New York: American Bank Note Company: 1889., 594; Size: 90.8 x 125.2 cm.; Colored.
    - Isogonic chart for the epoch 1890. U.S. Coast and Geodetic Survey. T. C. Mendenhall, superintendent. N.p.: [1890]., 595; Scale: 1:13,700,000.; Size: 24.5 x 52.6 cm.; Colored.; T. C. Mendenhall and C. A. Schott.
      At head of map: "Coast & Geodetic Survey Report for fiscal year 1888-'89."
    - Isogonic chart of the United States for the epoch 1890. U.S. Coast and Geodetic Survey. T. C. Mendenhall, superintendent. N.p.: [ca. 1890]., 596; Scale: 1:7,000,000.; Size: 55.5 x 71.6 cm.; Colored.; T. C. Mendenhall and C. A. Schott.
    - Magnetic meridians of the United States for January 1890. U.S. Coast and Geodetic Survey. T. C. Mendenhall, superintendent. N.p.: [1890]., 597; Scale: 1:10,000,000.; Size: 35.6 x 57.6 cm.; Colored.; T. C. Mendenhall and C. A. Schott.
    - Map of the United States and territories, with adjacent parts of Canada and Mexico also part of the West India Islands. Showing the extent of public surveys, Indian and military reservations, rail roads, canals, and other details. Compiled from the official surveys for the U. S. Department of the Interior General Land Office and other authentic sources... by A. F. Dinsmore. 1890. Baltimore: Isaac Friedenwald: 1890., 598; Scale: 1 in. = 40 statute mi.; Size: 158.4 x 204.2 cm.; Colored.; A. F. Dinsmore.
    - United States. Compiled under the direction of Henry Gannett... by Henry King. U.S. Department of the Interior. Geological Survey. [Washington]: 1898., 599; 3 sheets.; Scale: 1:2,500,000.; Size: 122.6 x 192.2 cm.; Colored.; Henry Gannett and Henry King.
      Inset: Alaska.
    - United States base map. Compiled by Henry Gannett. U.S. Geological Survey. J. W. Powell, director. [Washington]: 1899. Edition of Dec. 1896, reprinted Sept. 1899., 600; Scale: 9.1 cm. = 300 statute mi.; Size: 44.6 x 71.9 cm.; Colored.; Henry Gannett and J. W. Powell.; U.S. Geological Survey.
    - United States contour map. Compiled by Henry Gannett. U.S. Geological Survey. J. W. Powell, director. [Washington]: 1899. Edition of Dec. 1896, reprinted Sept. 1899., 601; Scale: 9.1 cm. = 300 statute mi.; Size: 44.5 x 71.9 cm.; Colored.; Henry Gannett and J. W. Powell.; U.S. Geological Survey.
    - United States relief map. Compiled by Henry Gannett. U.S. Geological Survey. J. W. Powell, director. [Washington]: 1899. Edition of Dec. 1896, reprinted September 1899., 602; Scale: 9.1 cm. = 300 statute mi.; Size: 44.4 x 71.9 cm.; Colored.; Henry Gannett and J. W. Powell.; U.S. Geological Survey.
    - Distribution of the magnetic declination in the United States in 1900. Compiled by Henry Gannett. U.S. Geological Survey. [Washington]: U.S. Geological Survey: [ca. 1901]., 603; Scale: 2.4 cm. = 100 mi.; Size: 44.5 x 71.8 cm.; Colored.; Henry Gannett.; U.S. Geological Survey.
      See: U.S. Geological Survey, 17th annual report, part I, pl. II.
    - Normal annual precipitation in the United States, 1870-1901. N.p.: [ca. 1902]., 604; Scale: 1 in. = 200 mi.; Size: 26 x 40.1 cm.; Colored.; Alfred J. Henry.; U.S. Geological Survey.
    - Climatic charts of the United States. U.S. Department of Agriculture. Weather Bureau. Washington: Weather Bureau: 1904., 605; Size of paper: 48.3 x 61.1 cm.; Colored.
      Contains title page and 26 charts.
    - United States. U.S. Geological Survey. Charles D. Walcott, director. [Washington]: 1906. Edition of May 1906., 606; Scale: 9.5 cm. = 600 mi.; Size: 26.5 x 40 cm.; Colored.; Charles D. Walcott.; U.S. Geological Survey.
    - United States including territories & insular possessions; showing the extent of public surveys, Indian, military & forest reservations, railroads, canals, national parks & other details. Compiled under the direction of I. P. Berthrong. U.S. General Land Office, Department of the Interior. Corrected to 30 June 1907. New York: Sackett & Wilhelms Co.: 1907., 607; Scale: 1 in. = 37 mi.; Size: 151 x 210 cm.; M. Hendges and I. P. Berthrong.; R. F. Bartle Co.
    - National forests with related projects and data. Base map compiled by the drafting division of the U.S. Department of Agriculture, General Land Office. Gifford Pinchot, Forester. Reissued with the national forests and related projects and data by the Office of Geography in the Forest Service. Information furnished by the U.S. Reclamation Service, U.S.Weather Bureau, and Inland Waterways Commission. [Washington]: 1908. Edition of 1 July 1908. Map of 4 sheets., 608; Scale: 1 in. = 37 mi.; Size: 150 x 208.2 cm.; Colored.
      Inset: Index map of most of the northern hemisphere; Panama Canal; Puerto Rico; Hawaiian Islands; Tutuila group of the Samoan Island; Guam or Cuajan Island; Philippine Islands; and Alaska with the Aleutian Islands.
    - Lines of the Bell Telephone Companies, United States and Canada, 1 July 1909. American Telephone and Telegraph Company. Boston: Heliotype Co.: 1909., 609; Scale: 1 in. = 40 mi.; Size: 136 x 198 cm.
    - United States. Original compiled under the direction of Henry Gannett. U.S. Geological Survey, George Otis Smith, director. 1910. [Washington]: 1910. First published in 1890., 610; 3 parts.; Scale: 1:2,500,000.; Size: 132.4 x 194.7 cm.; Colored.; Henry Gannett and George Otis Smith.
    - United States including territories and insular possessions; showing the extent of public surveys, Indian, military & forest reservations, railroads, canals, national parks.... U. S. General Land Office, Department of the Interior. Compiled under the direction of I. P. Berthrong. Corrected to 30 June 1910. New York: Sackett & Wilhelms Co.: 1910., 611; Scale: 1 in. = 37 mi.; Size: 148 x 207 cm.; M. Hendges and I. P. Berthrong.; R. F. Bartle Co.
    - United States. U.S. Geological Survey. George Otis Smith, director. [Washington]: U.S. Geological Survey: 1911. Edition of March 1911., 612; Scale: 3 cm. = 200 mi.; Size: 19.1 x 29.5 cm.; Colored.; George Otis Smith.
    - United States base map. Compiled by Henry Gannett. U.S. Geological Survey. George Otis Smith, director. [Washington]: 1911. Edition of November 1911., 613; Scale: 1:7,000,000.; Size: 44.6 x 72 cm.; Colored.; Henry Gannett and George Otis Smith.; U.S. Geological Survey.
    - United States contour map. Compiled by Henry Gannett. U.S. Geological Survey. George Otis Smith, director. [Washington]: 1911. Edition of Nov. 1911., 614; Scale: 1:7,000,000.; Size: 44.6 x 72.2 cm.; Colored.; Henry Gannett and George Otis Smith.; U.S. Geological Survey.
    - United States including territories and insular possessions; showing the extent of public surveys, Indian, military & forest reservations, railroads, canals, national parks.... U. S. General Land Office, Department of the Interior. Compiled under the direction of I. P. Berthrong. New York: Sackett & Wilhelms: 1913., 615; Scale: 1 in. = 37 mi.; Size: 150 x 208 cm.; I. P. Berthrong and M. Hendges.; R. F. Bartle Co.
    - United States. Original compilation under the direction of Henry Gannett. U.S. Geological Survey. George Otis Smith, director. [Washington]: U.S. Geological Survey: 1914. First published in 1890., 616; 2 sheets.; Scale: 1:2,500,000.; Size: 122.3 x 194.4 cm.; Colored.; Henry Gannett and George Otis Smith.; U.S. Geological Survey.
      Also map of type-of-farming areas in the United States, 1930.
    - Map of the United States showing locations of National Guard mobilization training camps; National Army cantonment camps; Reserve Officers training camps and aviation sites. Issued by the Rock Island Lines. Chicago: Rand McNally & Co.: [ca. 1916]., 617; Size: 49.1 x 90.7 cm.; Colored.
    - United States. Department of the Interior. Geological Survey. United States. [Washington]: U.S. Geological Survey: 1916. Edition of 1911, reprinted 1916., 618; Scale: 1 in. = 250 mi.; Size: 19.1 x 29.5 cm.; Colored.; U.S. Geological Survey.